sportskeeda.com 2015-12-25

# Privacy Policy

Sportskeeda is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information secure. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, we are fully disclosing our privacy practices. We encourage you to read our privacy statement to understand what types of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information. Sportskeeda has the right to amend its privacy policy to suit the needs of the website and we will inform you about the updated regulations at the earliest possible time.

**How we collect and use information**

Sportskeeda only collects the necessary personally identifiable information in order to respond to your requests for our customized products and services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, interests, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual.

This website does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. Sportskeeda uses your personally identifiable information to operate the site and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products from sportskeeda.com.

When you visit sportskeeda.com, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Sportskeeda help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the website (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the site), and allow us to track your usage of sportskeeda.com over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of sportskeeda.com may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Sportskeeda may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site’s service but are not necessary to its operation (an "Extended Service"). If Sportskeeda intends to use personally identifiable information for an Extended Service, the sportskeeda.com site will provide you with the ability and requisite instructions to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from sportskeeda.com by following the instructions on the mail.

Sportskeeda may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the site or its owners; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the site owners, the site or the users of sportskeeda.com, and (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of sportskeeda.com, the site, its owners, or the public.

**User/member interaction features**

sportskeeda.com has many features that provide for users/members to disclose their identities and communicate with other users/members. Your use of such features and disclosure of any personal details (e.g. e-mail address) by you through these features are at your sole risk and Sportskeeda accepts no responsibility for the same. However, if your privacy has been intruded as a result of participating in such features, you could notify us by e-mail at contact@sportskeeda.com.

**Other Websites**

The sportskeeda.com site contains links to other websites. Sportskeeda is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Notify Us**

If at any time you believe that sportskeeda.com or its users/members have not adhered to these principles, please notify Sportskeeda by e-mail at contact@sportskeeda.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

**Your Content**

The freedom to write articles of your choice (sports) allows you to present your views to the visitors through this platform. However, the bloggers, writers and authors are advised not to violate the copyright laws meant to promote original work. The website will not be responsible for any content posted by its users. However, we will take appropriate action against copied content, if any, reported by a visitor.

The content on this website is published merely to enable sharing of ideas among people and to bring awareness about sports to the masses. The views expressed by the bloggers, authors or writers are their opinions and do not stand to be used as legal evidence.

    The above privacy policy applies to all of Sportskeeda's platforms, including the mobile apps for Android, Windows and iOS.
